Greenbaum, Marcia Papers 6091
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Beloit Corporation ARB 1994 and AAA #11 300 01826 94 UE, Local 212 Suspension, 1994-1995 (Box 83, Folder 3)
- Boise Cascade Corp. ARB 1994 and AAA #11 300 00303 94 #3013 UPIU, Local 900 Discharge (Box 83, Folder 4)
- Boise Cascade Corp. ARB 1994 UPIU, Local 900 #2146A Regressn., 1995 (Box 83, Folder 5)
- Boston Municipal Police Patrolmen's Association, and the City of Boston, 1994 (Box 83, Folder 6)
- Boston Municipal Police Patrolmen's Association, and The City of Boston- II, 1994 (Box 83, Folder 7)
- Boston Municipal Police Patrolmen's Association, and The City of Boston- III and IV, 1994 (Box 83, Folder 8)
- City of Boston Fact Finding 94 and PS-162-1994 (Patrol Offcrs Municipal Police Patrolmen's Assn), 1995-1996 (Box 83, Folder 9)
- Agreement between City of Boston and Municipal Boston Police Patrolmen's Association JX1-JX-3, 1985-1990 (Box 84, Folder 1)
- Boston Police Superior Officers Federation and City of Boston J x 4, 1994 (Box 84, Folder 2)
- Boston Police Patrolmen's Association and City of Boston J x 5, 1994 (Box 84, Folder 3)
- Locations for Which Patrol Officers Are Responsible and Memorandum Agreement City of Boston and Boston Police Detectives Benevolent Society J x6- J x 8, 1993-1996 (Box 84, Folder 4)
- Memorandum of Agreement Between Boston Housing Authority and International Brotherhood of Police Officers- Local 408 and City of Boston and Municipal Police Superior Officers Association J x 9-J x10, 1993-1996 (Box 84, Folder 5)
- City Proposal, Securing Boston's Financial Health and Special Report City x 1- City x 3, 1992-1994 (Box 84, Folder 6)
- Documents Relating to Boston Police and the City of Boston, 1994 (Box 84, Folder 7)
- Assn. X 11 Bureau of Justice Assistance, 1987-1992 (Box 84, Folder 8)
- Boston School Committee ARB 1994 and AAA #11 390 01267 94 Dismissal, 1991-1997 (Box 84, Folder 9)
- Agreement Between the School Committee of the City of Boston and the Boston Teachers Union, Local 66, AFT, AFL-CIO, 1993- 1994 (Box 84, Folder 10)
- Arbitration Awards, 1978-1989 (Box 84, Folder 11)
- Boston School Committee Vol. I, 1994 (Box 84, Folder 12)
- Boston School Committee Vol. II, 1995 (Box 84, Folder 13)
- Boston School Committee Vol. III, 1995 (Box 84, Folder 14)
- Boston School Committee Vol. IV and V, 1995 (Box 84, Folder 15)
- Brattleboro Retreat ARB 1994 and AAA #11 300 00630 94 F. Nurses and Health Prof., Loc. 5086 (Box 84, Folder 16)
- Town of Bristol, RI ARB 1994 and AAA #10 390 0200 94 Raposa I.B.P.O. Detail Rate Comp., 1995 (Box 84, Folder 17)
- Bristol, RI ARB 1994 and AAA #10 390 0202 94 Walpole I.B.P.O., 1994-1996 (Box 84, Folder 18)
- Brookline, MA School Comm. ARB 94 and AAA #11 390 01850 94 Repr. Brookline Educators Assn. Dudley, 1994-1995 (Box 84, Folder 19)
- Central Maine Power Co. ARB 1994 and AAA #11 300 00980 94 IBEW, Local 1837 (Folder 1 of 2) (Box 84, Folder 20)
- Central Maine Power Co. ARB 1994 and AAA #11 300 00980 94 IBEW, Local 1837 (Folder 2 of 2) (Box 84, Folder 21)
- Central Vermont Public Service COR and AAA #11 300 00461 94 ARB IBEW, Local 300 Contracting Out, 1995 (Box 84, Folder 22)
- Colchester, VT School Board ARB and Direct Scheduling Griev.. Colchester, VT. Teachers VT/NEA, 1994-1995 (Box 84, Folder 23)
- Conn. BD. Of Trustees OF. Tech. and 1994 Colleges FEDN. Of Tech. Coll. Teachers (Folder 1 of 2), 1985-1996 (Box 85, Folder 1)
- Conn. BD. Of Trustees OF. Tech. and 1994 Colleges FEDN. Of Tech. Coll. Teachers (Folder 2 of 2), 1992-1995 (Box 85, Folder 2)
- Continental Baking Company 1994 and AAA #11 300 00236 94 BCT and TW Local 348 bid to 1.g 2 (Box 85, Folder 3)
- City of Coral Gables, FL ARB 94 and FMCS #94-06967 drvr/eg trg IAFF, Local 1210, 1994 (Box 85, Folder 4)
- Danbury, CT. Board of EDN. ARB 94 and AAA #12 390 00477 94 Danbury Teachers, NEA Complaint, 1994-1995 (Box 85, Folder 5)
- Dedham School Committee ARB 94 and AAA #11 390 01714 93 Dedham Education Assn. Evaln., 1993-1995 (Box 85, Folder 6)
- Duxbury School Committee ARB 1994 and AAA #11 390 00451 94 Duxbury Teachers Assn., 1994-1995 (Box 85, Folder 7)
- Emery Worldwide ARB 1994 and AAA #11 300 00161 94 Pay Intl. Bro. of Teamsters, Local 251 (Box 85, Folder 8)
- Exeter-West Greenwich Rgnl SD 94 and AAA #11 390 02373 94 E-WGRSD Teachers Assn,/NEARI, 1995 (Box 85, Folder 9)
- Federal Deposit Ins. Corp. ARB 94 and FMCS # 95-01858 Woodbury Vener Natl. Treas. EES UN., Chapter 263, 1994-1995 (Box 85, Folder 10)
- Furon/CHR Industries, Inc. 1994 and FMCS #94-12792 Dis URW Local 231 Discharge (Folder 1 of 2), 1993-1995 (Box 85, Folder 11)
- Furon/CHR Industries, Inc. 1994 and FMCS #94-12792 Dis URW Local 231 Discharge (Folder 2 of 2), 1993-1995 (Box 85, Folder 12)
- Volume I CHR Industries, Inc. and Local Union No. 231 United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum and Plastic Workers of America, 1994 (Box 85, Folder 13)
- Volume II and III CHR Industries, Inc. and Local Union No. 231 United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum and Plastic Workers of America, 1994- 1995 (Box 85, Folder 14)
- GAF materials Corp. ARB 1994 and FMCS #94-23147 UPIU Local 50458 Make-Up OVRTM, 1995 (Box 85, Folder 15)
- Gloucester Engineering Co 1994 and AAA #11 300 00 1974 93 IAM, Lodge (Box 85, Folder 16)
- Great Northern Paper Co. ARB 1994 and AAA #11 300 01794 93 Pay OPEIU, Local 192 (Box 85, Folder 17)
- GTE Southwest Brownwood, TX 94 and AAA #71 300 00033 94 CWA Gr. #6-93-315 Bumping rts, 1996-1997 (Box 85, Folder 18)
- Communication Workers of America Vs. GTE Southwest, Inc., Brownwood, Texas, 1996 (Box 85, Folder 19)
- Hartford, CT Board of Education and AAA #12 390 00181 94 Hartford Federation of Teachers, 1994 (Box 85, Folder 20)
- Haverhill Paperboard Co. ARB 1994 and AAA #11 300 00768 94 \AAA #11 300 00768 94 UPIU, Local 204 Discharge, 1994-1995 (Box 85, Folder 21)
- Intertech Resources, Inc. ARB 94 and FMCS #94-04150 Seniority ICWU, Local 975 FT. Myers, 1994 (Box 85, Folder 22)
- John Hancock Ins. Co. ARB 1994 and AAA #11 300 0068 94 United Food and Commercial Workers (Box 85, Folder 23)
- Keyes Fibre Co. (Van Leer) ARB 94 and FMCS #93-27357 Gr. 93-13 UPIU, Local 449 Restoration of Fo, 1994 (Box 85, Folder 24)
- City of Lunn, MA ARB 1994 and AAA #11 390 0500 94 Pay Lynn Firefighters Local 739 (Box 85, Folder 25)
- City of Lynn, MA ARB 1994 and AAA #11 390 0501 94 Failure to Lynn Firefighters, Loc. 739 Inst. (Box 85, Folder 26)
- State of Maine ARB 1994 and AAA #11 390 00475 94 B. U. MSEA Exclusions, 1994-1995 (Box 85, Folder 27)
- Maine State Retirement System 1994 and AAA #11 390 01497 94 Longevity Maine State Employees Assn. (Box 85, Folder 28)
- Maine Yankee Automatic Power Co. and AAA #11 300 01033 94 Contrtr Utility Workers UA, Loc. 497 INFR, 1994-1995 (Box 85, Folder 29)
- New England Telephone Gr. MEDN 94 AND Suspension MREP 62 IBEW, Local 2322, 1994 (Box 85, Folder 30)
- South Shore Vocational Regional and School District Pay South Shore Voc. Teachers FEDN., 1995 (Box 85, Folder 31)
- Sweet Life Food ARB 1994 and AAA #12 300 00126 94 Teamsters, Local 559 Sen. Pref., 1995 (Box 85, Folder 32)
- U.S. Dept. of the Air Force 1994 and FMCS #94-16503 Privacy Act NAGE, Local R1-8 Hanscom AFB (Box 85, Folder 33)
- US Immigration and Naturalization and FMCS 94-17952 AFGE, Local 2580, 1994-1995 (Box 85, Folder 34)
- Worcester Polytechnical Inst. ARB and AAA #11 300 00961 94 Discip. SEIU, Local 254, 1994-1995 (Box 85, Folder 35)
- City of Miramar, FL ARB 1994 and FMCS #94-06173 Sick Leave G.A.M.E. Blue Book (Box 86, Folder 1)
- New England Telephone Gr. MEDN. 94 and Termination IBEW, Local #2222 MREP, 1994 (Box 86, Folder 2)
- New England Telephone Gr. MED. 94 and MREP 68 Suspension IBEW, Local 2320, 1993-1994 (Box 86, Folder 3)
- New England Telephone Gr. Med. 94 and MREP 69 Suspension IBEW, Local 2320, 1993-1994 (Box 86, Folder 4)
- New England Telephone Gr. Med. 94 and MREP 70 Suspension IBEW, Local 2320, 1993-1994 (Box 86, Folder 5)
- UNIV. of New Hampshire ARB 1994 and AAA #11 390 00685 94 AAUP/ UNH Chapter Payment (Folder 1 of 2), 1994-1995 (Box 86, Folder 6)
- UNIV. of New Hampshire ARB 1994 and AAA #11 390 00685 94 AAUP/ UNH Chapter Payment (Folder 2 of 2), 1994-1995 (Box 86, Folder 7)
- University System of New Hampshire and African Association of University Professors/ University of New Hampshire Chapter (Folder 1 of 2), 1992-1993 (Box 86, Folder 8)
- University System of New Hampshire and African Association of University Professors/ University of New Hampshire Chapter (Folder 2 of 2), 1992-1993 (Box 86, Folder 9)
- No. Kingstown School Comm. ARB 94 and AAA #11 390 01404 94 No. Kingstown ESP/ NEARI Promotion, 1994-1995 (Box 86, Folder 10)
- City of Peabody, MA ARB 1994 and AAA #11 390 00705 94 94-04 Peabody Police Benevolent Assn., 1994-1995 (Box 86, Folder 11)
- Pepsi-Cola Company ARB 1994 and FMCS #94-04072 USWA, Local Discharge, 1993 (Box 86, Folder 12)
- The Pepsi-Cola Company and United Steelworkers of America Local Union 8430-Sales `, 1994 (Box 86, Folder 13)
- City of Providence, RI ARB 1994 and AAA #11 390 01970 94 BU Work RILDC, 10CAL 1033 Water Plt. Mec., 1995 (Box 86, Folder 14)
- Providence, RI School Comm. ARB 94 and AAA #11 390 01084 94 Cook RILDC, Local 1033 TA BU 4/94 Reces, 1994-1995 (Box 86, Folder 15)
- Providence Journal CO. ARB 1994 and AAA #11 300 01943 94 Gr. #7-94 Providence Newspaper Guild expense, 1995 (Box 86, Folder 16)
- City of Quincy, MA ARB 1994 and AAA #11 390 00536 94 Quincy Police Patrol Officers Assn. (Box 86, Folder 17)
- Raytheon Computer Sciences ARB and FCMS #94-17191 B.U. Work IBEW, Local 2088, 1994-1995 (Box 86, Folder 18)
- Raytheon Company ARB 1994 and Vision Care Benefit Timing I.B.E.W., Local 1505, 1987-1994 (Box 86, Folder 19)
- State of Rhode Island ARB 1994 and AAA #11 390 01383 94 93-193 DCYF C/A G8413 SALVO/ WREN, 1991-1997 (Box 86, Folder 20)
- Rhode Island Hospital ARB 1994 and AAA #11 300 02243 94 Termn. RI FNHP, 1995 (Box 86, Folder 21)
- Rose Auto Stores ARB 1994 and FMCS 94-07531 OT Pay I.B. Teamsters, local 769 MIA (Box 86, Folder 22)
- Shaw's Supermarkets, Inc. 1994 and AAA #11 300 00029 94 FT United Food and Comm. Workers 791, 1994-1995 (Box 86, Folder 23)
- Shaw's Supermarkets, Inc. ARB 94 and AAA #11 300 00053 94 UFCW, Local 791 Suspension, 1993-1994 (Box 86, Folder 24)
- Shaw's Supermarkets, Inc. ARB 94 and AAA #11 300 00326 94 U.F.C.W., Local 791 Termination, 1994 (Box 86, Folder 25)
- Shaw's Supermarkets, Inc. ARBN 94 and AAA #11 300 0327 94 United Food and Commercial Workers, 1994 (Box 86, Folder 26)
- Shaw's Supermarkets, Inc. ARB 94 and AAA #11 300 00335 94 UFCW, Local 791 #757, 1994 (Box 86, Folder 27)
- Shaw's Supermarkets, Inc. ARB 1994 and AAA #11 300 00519 94 UFCW, Local 791 Warnings and Susp., 1994-1995 (Box 86, Folder 28)
- Shaw's Supermarkets, Inc. ARB 1994 and AAA #11 300 00647 94 #776 UFCW, Local 791 Trans (Box 86, Folder 29)
- Shaw's Supermarkets, Inc. ARB 1992 and AAA #11 300 00650 94 #778 UFCW, Local 791 Termination, 1994 (Box 86, Folder 30)
- Shaw's Supermarkets, Inc. ARB 1994 and AAA #11 300 00831 94 and UFCW, Local 791, 1994- 1995 (Box 86, Folder 31)
- Shaw's Supermarkets, Inc. ARB 1994 and AAA #11 300 01510 94 #806 UFCW, Local 791 Sun. and Hol. Work, 1995 (Box 86, Folder 32)
- Shaw's Supermarkets, Inc. ARB 1994 and AAA #11 300 01520 94 Gr. #813 UFCW, Local 791 (Box 86, Folder 33)
- Shaw's Supermarkets, Inc. ARB 1994 and AAA #11 300 01521 94 Gr. #814 UFCW, Local 791 (Box 86, Folder 34)
- Shaw's Supermarkets, Inc. ARB 1994 and AAA #11 300 01951 94 #835 UFCW, Loc. 791 Term., 1995 (Box 86, Folder 35)
- Shaw's Supermarkets, Inc. ARB 94 and AAA #11 300 01959 94 #815 UFCW, Local 791 OT Holiday Wk., 1995 (Box 86, Folder 36)
- Town of Smithfield, RI ARB 1994 and AAA #11 390 01492 94 RILDC, Local 1217 Medical Coverage, 1995 (Box 86, Folder 37)
- Sweet Life Foods ARB 1994 and 12 300 00002 94 I.B. Teamsters, Loc. 559 Seniort, 1995 (Box 86, Folder 38)
- Teamsters Local 559 and Sweet Life Foods, Inc. Case No. 12-300-002-94, 1994 (Box 87, Folder 1)
- Cambridge Teachers Association and Cambridge School Committee Grievance: Demotion Vol. IX and X, 1995 (Box 87, Folder 2)
- Cambridge Teachers Association and Cambridge School Committee Grievance: Demotion Vol. VII and VIII, 1995 (Box 87, Folder 3)
- Cambridge Teachers Association and Cambridge School Committee Grievance: Demotion Vol. V and VI, 1995 (Box 87, Folder 4)
- Cambridge Teachers Association and Cambridge School Committee Grievance: Demotion Vol. IV and III, 1994 (Box 87, Folder 5)
- Cambridge Teachers Association and Cambridge School Committee Grievance: Demotion Vol. I, 1994 (Box 87, Folder 6)
- Cambridge Teachers Association and Cambridge School Committee Grievance: Demotion Vol. II, 1994 (Box 87, Folder 7)
- Cambridge Teachers Association and Cambridge School Committee Grievance, 1996 (Box 87, Folder 8)
- Cambridge Teachers Association and Cambridge School Committee Grievance: Demotion, 1996 (Box 87, Folder 9)
- Cambridge School Comm. CondenseIt, 1991 (Box 87, Folder 10)
- Cambridge School Committee A 94 AAA #11 390 01074 94 Cambridge Teachers Assn. Demotion, 1993-1996 (Box 87, Folder 11)
- Town of Duxbury, MA ARB 1994 and AAA #11 390 00223 94 I.B.P.O., Local 323 Term, 1994-2001 (Box 88, Folder 1)
- Town of Duxbury Duxbury, Massachusetts and International Brotherhood of Police Officers, Local 323, 2001 (Box 88, Folder 2)
- Town of Duxbury Duxbury, Massachusetts and International Brotherhood of Police Officers, Local 323 AAA #11 390 00223 94, 2001 (Box 88, Folder 3)
- AAA 11-390-00223-94 I.B.P.O., Local 323 and Town of Duxbury Grievance: Termination (Box 88, Folder 4)
- AAA 11-390-00223-94 I.B.P.O., Local 323 and Town of Duxbury Grievance: Termination. (Box 88, Folder 5)
- AAA 11-390-00223-94 I.B.P.O., Local 323 and Town of Duxbury Grievance: Termination and Other Related Docs., 2001 (Box 88, Folder 6)
- Town of Duxbury, Massachusetts and International Brotherhood of Police Officers, Local 323 and Twelfth Hearing, 1995-2001 (Box 88, Folder 7)
- Town of Duxbury Transcript, 2001 (Box 88, Folder 8)
- Town of Duxbury Duxbury, Massachusetts and International Brotherhood of Police Officers, Local 323, 2001 (Box 88, Folder 9)
- Town of Duxbury, MA and IBPO, Local 323 and other docs., 1995 (Box 88, Folder 10)
- Commonwealth V. Defendant and Other docs., 1991-1994 (Box 88, Folder 11)
- Commonwealth of Massachusetts (Folder 1 of 3), 1993 (Box 88, Folder 12)
- Commonwealth of Massachusetts (Folder 2 of 3), 1993 (Box 88, Folder 13)
- Commonwealth of Massachusetts (Folder 3 of 3), 1993 (Box 88, Folder 14)
- Floppy Disks (2) (Box 88, Folder 15)
- Exhibit "C" Testimony Excerpts, 1993 (Box 89, Folder 1)
- Exhibit "B" Testimony Excerpts, 1991-1993 (Box 89, Folder 2)
- Docs. Relating to Duxbury Police Department, 1989-1994 (Box 89, Folder 3)
- Documents Relating to Massachusetts Commonwealth, 1986-1994 (Box 89, Folder 4)
- Documents Relating to The Town of Duxbury, Massachusetts, 2001 (Box 89, Folder 5)
- Documents Relating to the Town of Duxbury and Police Officers, 1998 (Box 89, Folder 6)
- Documents Relating to the Commonwealth of Massachusetts and Dormady, 1992-1995 (Box 89, Folder 7)
- Docs. Relating to Duxbury and Dormady, 1994 (Box 89, Folder 8)
- RE: 11 390 00223 94 I.B.P.O., Local 323 and Town of Duxbury Grievance: termination, 2001 (Box 89, Folder 9)
- UN Stipulated Exhibits and Admitted Exhibits, 1994 (Box 89, Folder 10)
- Hilda Grace, Plaintiff, v. Defendants CA NO. 93-1553 B, 1993 (Box 89, Folder 11)
- Avon, CT. BD. Of Education 1995 and AAA #12 390 00390 95 Letter National Assn. of Govt. EES Rep., 1996 (Box 89, Folder 12)
- Abington School Committee ARB 1995 and AAA #11 390 00576 95 Hayes Abington Education Assn. and Mayhew (Box 89, Folder 13)
- Acton, MA School Committee ARB 95 and AAA #11 390 02099 95 DePillo Action Education Assn. Evaluation, 1996 (Box 89, Folder 14)
- Arbitration of Grievance of Patricia DiPillo and Acton Educators Association, Against Acton-Boxborough School District, 1996 (Box 89, Folder 15)
- Boise Cascade Corporation ARB 1995 and AAA #11 300 00175 95 #5025 UPIU, Local 900 Discharge (Box 89, Folder 16)
- Boise Cascade Corporation ARB 1995 and AAA #11 300 02009 94 #1012 UPIU, Local 9000 Unjust Discipline (Box 89, Folder 17)
- Boston Edison CO. ARB 1995 and AAA #11 300 0082 95 Disch. UWUA Local 369 Susp. (Box 89, Folder 18)
- Boston Edison Company and Local 369, Utility Workers Union of America AFL-CIO Vol. I, 1995 (Box 89, Folder 19)
- Boston Edison Company and Local 369, Utility Workers Union of America AFL-CIO Vol. II, 1995 (Box 89, Folder 20)
- Boston Edison Company and Local 369, Utility Workers Union of America AFL-CIO Vol. III, 1995 (Box 89, Folder 21)
- Boston Housing Authority ARB 1995 and AAA #11 390 01574 95 W. Caban IB Teamsters, Local 122 Termination., 1995-1996 (Box 89, Folder 22)
- Boston School Committee ARB 1995 and AAA #11 390 02136 94 B.P.S.B.C.A. Custodian Mad. Park (Box 89, Folder 23)
- Boston School Committee ARB 1994 and AAA #11 390 01615 94 Gordon Boston Teachers Union, Local 66, 1996 (Box 89, Folder 24)
- Central Maine Power CO. ARB 1995 and AAA #11 300 01457 95 Dube IBEW, Local 1837 (Box 89, Folder 25)
- State of Connecticut ARB 1995 and AAA #123 0000595 CSEA Interest Arbitration (Box 90, Folder 1)
- State of Connecticut and Connecticut State Employees Association P-3A Unit- Interest Arbitration, 1995 (Box 90, Folder 2)
- Residual Bargaining Unit and Docs. Relating to State of Connecticut and Connecticut State Employees Association, 1995-1999 (Box 90, Folder 3)
- CSFA. Inc. and State of Connecticut P-3A Unit and P-3A Contract, 1988-1994 (Box 90, Folder 4)
- Agreement between The State of Connecticut and The State Coalition Pay Equity, A State Employee Reference Guide, 1992- 1994 (Box 90, Folder 5)
- Documents Relating to the State of Connecticut: Arbitration Cases, 1994-1996 (Box 90, Folder 6)
- Documents Relating to the Economy of the State of Connecticut and Department of Education, 1995-1997 (Box 90, Folder 7)
- Connecticut BD. Of Trustees Of Community- Technical Colleges and FEDN. Of Technical Coll. Teachers, 1990-1996 (Box 90, Folder 8)
- Cranston, RI School Committee 95 and AAA #11 39 01929 95 Coaching Cranston Teachers' Alliance Incr., 1995-1996 (Box 90, Folder 9)
- Town of Dedham, MA ARB 1995 and AAA #11 390 00902 95 Dedham Police Assn. F. Rielawski, 1996 (Box 90, Folder 10)
- East Bridgewater, MA School Comm. And AAA #11 390 01446 95 ARB East Bridgewater Education Assn., 1995-1996 (Box 90, Folder 11)
- Energy north Natural Gas, Inc. 1995 and Gr. No. 94-C-2 Direct USWA, Local Union NO. 12012 (Box 90, Folder 12)
- Erving Paper Company ARB 1995 and AAA #11 300 01898 95 Welcome UPIU, Local 594 Return to Work, 1996 (Box 90, Folder 13)
- 11 300 01898 95 UPIU, Local 594 and Erving Paper Company and Harvard Medical School Health Letter, 1995-1996 (Box 90, Folder 14)
- Town of Foster, RI ARB 1995 and AAA#11 390 00753 95 #95-01 IBPO, Local (Box 90, Folder 15)
- GTE Southwest, Inc. ARB 1995 and AAA #71 300 00072 95 CWA, Gr. #6-95-23, 1996 (Box 90, Folder 16)
- The Arbitration: Communication Workers of America and GTE Southwest, Incorporated Grievance No. 6-95-23, 1990 (Box 90, Folder 17)
- Communication Workers of America Vs. GTE Southwest, Inc. Grievance No. 6-95-23, 1996 (Box 90, Folder 18)
- Communications Workers of America VS. GTE Southwest, Inc. Grievance NO. 6-95-23, 1996 (Box 91, Folder 1)
- Grievance #WS-94-20 SV Bumping Rights Brownfield/ Littlefield Division, 1996 (Box 91, Folder 2)
- Greater Bridgeport Transit District and AAA #12 300 37 95 Gr. #52-94 AMAL. Transit Union, Local 1336, 1995 (Box 91, Folder 3)
- Hannaford Bros. Company ARB 1995 and AAA #11 300 01934 95 Hansen UFCW, Local 1292 #94-09091, 10-01, 1995-1996 (Box 91, Folder 4)
- Hartford, CT. BD. Of ED. ARB 1995 and AAA #12 390 00197 95 Dischg Hartford FEDN. Of Paraprofessional, 1996 (Box 91, Folder 5)
- Hartford, CT. Board of ED. ARB 95 and AAA #12 390 00202 95 #94-020 Hartford Federation of Teachers, 1995 (Box 91, Folder 6)
- Hartford, CT. Board of Education and AAA #12 E 390 00322 95 ARB Hartford FEDN. Of Teachers C1. Size, 1996 (Box 91, Folder 7)
- Hartford, CT. BD. of Education AAA #12 390 00326 95 Hartford Federation of Teachers, 1995 (Box 91, Folder 8)
- Jackson Memorial Hospital ARB 95 and FMCS #95 11559 SEIU, Local 1991 Shift Selection, 1995-1996 (Box 91, Folder 9)
- James Ferrera and Sons ARB 1995 and FMCS #95-12055 IBT, Local 829 (Box 91, Folder 10)
- James River Corporation ARB 1995 and AAA #11 300 00215 95 Wage UPIU, Local 80 Adjustment, 1996 (Box 91, Folder 11)
- Laidlaw Transit ARB 1995 and AAA #11 390 01794 95 NEHCEU, District 1199 IV, 2 XI, 8 (Box 91, Folder 12)
- Town of Lexington, MA ARB 1995 and AAA #11 390 0204 95 Health Ins Lexington Firefighters Loc. 1491 (Box 91, Folder 13)
- Ludlow, MA School Comm. ARB 1995 and AAA #11 390 02314 95 Schulze Ludlow Education Assn. Work day/ yr, 1996 (Box 91, Folder 14)
- City of Lynn, MA ARB 1995 and AAA #11 390 02420 94 Lynn Police Association, 1996 (Box 91, Folder 15)
- Malden, MA ARB 1995 and AAA #11 390 01318 95 Malden Police Patrolmen's Assn., 1996 (Box 91, Folder 16)
- Marriott Management Services ARB 95 and AAA #11 300 00116 95 Dischrg SEIU, Local 254, 1995 (Box 91, Folder 17)
- Mass Elec. and NEPSC ARB 95 and BUWNE, Local 330 Discharge, 1995-1996 (Box 91, Folder 18)
- Memorial Hospital ARB 1995 and AAA #11300 01862 95 On-call FNHP, Local 5082, 1995-1996 (Box 91, Folder 19)
- New Boston Garden ARB 1995 and AAA #11 300 00633 95 Terminatr SEIU, Local 254 (Box 91, Folder 20)
- New Britain BD. Of ED. ARB 1995 and AAA #12 390 00448 94 Spec. Ed. New Britain FEDN. Of Teachers; 877 (Box 91, Folder 21)
- New England Power Service Co. 95 and Use of Outside Contractor BUWNE, Local #345 Revenue Acctg., 1995 (Box 91, Folder 22)
- New England Power Service Co. 1995 and Narragansett Electric Co. BUWNE, Local #345 Jr. ACCT. Plant (Box 91, Folder 23)
- New England Power Service CO. ARB and Failure to Fill Vacancy UWUA, Local #264 Gr. #95-13, 1996 (Box 91, Folder 24)
- New England Telephone NYNEX 1995 and MREP #72 Suspensn IBEW, Local 2322 Gr. #123-93, 1994 (Box 91, Folder 25)
- New England Telephone NYNEX 1995 and MREP #75 Termination IBEW, Local 2322 Gr. #187-93, 1994 (Box 91, Folder 26)
- New England Telephone NYNEX 1995 and MREP # 76 Suspension IBEW, Local 23222 GR. #16-94, 1994 (Box 91, Folder 27)
- New England Telephone NYEX 1995 and MREP #77 Termination IBEW, Local 2321 GR. #T-12-94, 1994 (Box 91, Folder 28)
- New England Telephone NYEX 1995 and MREP #78 Termn. IBEW, Local 2321 GR. #P-10-94, 1994-1995 (Box 91, Folder 29)
- New England Telephone NYEX 1995 and MREP #79 Unfair disc IBEW, Local 2222 Gr. #PC-06-94, 1993-1994 (Box 91, Folder 30)
- NYNEX Grievance MEDN. 1995 and Suspension IBEW, Local 2222 (Box 91, Folder 31)
- State University of New York 95 and OER No. 93-08-0095 United University Professions, 1995 (Box 91, Folder 32)
- State University of New York ARB 95 and OER #94-08-255 United University Professions, 1995-1996 (Box 91, Folder 33)
- State University of New York ARB and OER #94-08-829 United University Professions, 1996 (Box 91, Folder 34)
- State of New York (Albany) ARB 1995 and SUNY #94-023 OER #94-08-872 UUP #93-2724, 1996 (Box 91, Folder 35)
- OSRAM Sylvania, Inc. ARB 1995 and FMCS #95-17976 Subcontracting IBT, Local 42 Overtime (Box 91, Folder 36)
- PCT Services, Inc. ARB 1995 and FMCS #95-19093 IBT, Local 769 Discharge, 1995-1996 (Box 91, Folder 37)
- City of Providence, RI ARB 1995 and AAA #11 390 0476 95 Board RILDC Loc. 1033 OT Water Sup (Box 91, Folder 38)
- City of Providence, RI ARB 1995 and AAA #11 390 01673 95 RILDC, Local 1033 Lockout WSB, 1995-1996 (Box 91, Folder 39)
- Providence Journal CO. ARB 1995 and AAA #11 300 00746 95 Prov. Newsp. PRTG Pressman's #12 (Box 91, Folder 40)
- State of Rhode Island ARB 1995 and AAA #11 390 00098 95 #94-60 Rhode Island ASSE ER C/A G8961, 1994-1995 (Box 91, Folder 41)